phishcheck.me 2018-01-14

# Phishcheck 2.0 beta - Privacy Policy

Our privacy policy applies to information we collect when you use or access our website, application, or just interact with us. We may change this privacy policy from time to time. Whenever we make changes to this privacy policy, the changes are effective 30 days after we post the revised privacy policy (as indicated by revising the date at the top of our privacy policy). We encourage you to review our privacy policy whenever you access our services to stay informed about our information practices and the ways you can help protect your privacy. 

## Collection of Information

### Information We Collect Automatically When You Use the Services

When you access or use our services, we automatically collect information about you, including: 

  * Log Information: We log information about your use of our services, including the type of browser you use, access times, pages viewed, your IP address and the page you visited before navigating to our services.
  * Device Information: We collect information about the computer you use to access our services, including the hardware model, and operating system and version.
  * Location Information: We may collect information about the location of your device each time you access or use our website or otherwise consent to the collection of this information.

Information Collected by Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies: We use various technologies to collect information, and this may include sending cookies to your computer. Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive or in your device memory that helps us to improve our services and your experience, see which areas and features of our services are popular and count visits. We may also collect information using web beacons (also known as "tracking pixels"). Web beacons are electronic images that may be used in our services or emails and to track count visits or understand usage and campaign effectiveness. 

For more details about how we collect information, including details about cookies and how to disable them, please see "Your Information Choices" below. 

### Information We Collect From Other Sources

In order to provide you with access to the Service, or to provide you with better service in general, we may combine information obtained from other sources (for example, a third-party service whose application you have authorized or used to sign in) and combine that with information we collect through our services. 

### Use of Information

We use information about you for various purposes, including to: 

  * Provide, maintain and improve our services;
  * Respond to your comments, questions and requests and provide customer service;
  * Monitor and analyze trends, usage and activities in connection with our services; and Personalize and improve our services.

By accessing and using our services, you consent to the processing and transfer of your information in and to the United States and other countries. 

### Sharing of Information

We may share personal information about you as follows: 

  * With third party vendors and other service providers who need access to your information to carry out work on our behalf, such as Google Analytics, Google Adense, and DoubleClick.
  * If we believe disclosure is reasonably necessary to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request;
  * To enforce applicable user agreements or policies, including our Terms of Service located at http://phishcheck.me//terms-of-service/; and to protect us, our users or the public from harm or illegal activities;
  * In connection with any merger, sale of PhishCheckMe assets, financing or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company;
  * If we notify you through our services (or in our privacy policy) that the information you provide will be shared in a particular manner and you provide such information.

We may also share aggregated or anonymized information that does not directly identify you. 

### Third Party Analytics

We may allow third parties to provide analytics services. These third parties may use cookies, web beacons and other technologies to collect information about your use of the services and other websites, including your IP address, web browser, pages viewed, time spent on pages, links clicked and conversion information. This information may be used by us and third parties to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content and other websites and better understand your online activity. Our privacy policy does not apply to, and we are not responsible for, third party cookies, web beacons or other tracking technologies and we encourage you to check the privacy policies of these third parties to learn more about their privacy practices. 

## Security

We take reasonable measures to help protect personal information from loss, theft, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. 

## Your Information Choices

### Cookies

Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove or reject browser cookies. Please note that if you choose to remove or reject cookies, this could affect the availability and functionality of our services. 

## Contact Us

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us at: admin@phishcheck.me.
